customermagnetism.com 2012-05-05

# Customer Magnetism Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for [www.customermagnetism.com](http://www.customermagnetism.com/ "Customer Magnetism"). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you sometime in the future via email or phone to follow up on your interest of our services and/or to tell you about specials, new products, new services, or changes to this privacy policy.

Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

If you aware of any abuse of this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 757-689-2875 or via email at [sales@trycm.com](mailto:sales@trycm.com).

**GREAT IDEA: WATCH OUR VIDEO**
